{
    "questions": [
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "3 + 4 = ",
        "optiona": "12",
        "optionb": "5",
        "optionc": "7",
        "optiond": "9",
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "id": 1
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "4 + 4 =",
        "optiona": "4",
        "optionb": "7",
        "optionc": "10",
        "optiond": "8",
        "correctAnswer": "d",
        "id": 2
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "5 + 7 =",
        "optiona": "13",
        "optionb": "11",
        "optionc": "12",
        "optiond": "14",
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "id": 3
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "11 + 12 =",
        "optiona": "23",
        "optionb": "32",
        "optionc": "25",
        "optiond": "22",
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "id": 4
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "13 + 7 =",
        "optiona": "21",
        "optionb": "12",
        "optionc": "14",
        "optiond": "20",
        "correctAnswer": "d",
        "id": 5
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "15 + 5 =",
        "optiona": "21",
        "optionb": "12",
        "optionc": "20",
        "optiond": "19",
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "id": 6
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "14 + 4 =",
        "optiona": "18",
        "optionb": "8",
        "optionc": "12",
        "optiond": "22",
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "id": 7
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "13 + 3 =",
        "optiona": "19",
        "optionb": "12",
        "optionc": "16",
        "optiond": "9",
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "id": 8
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "4 + 9 =",
        "optiona": "13",
        "optionb": "12",
        "optionc": "19",
        "optiond": "17",
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "id": 9
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "16 + 6 =",
        "optiona": "18",
        "optionb": "22",
        "optionc": "12",
        "optiond": "19",
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "id": 10
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "question": "12 + 7 =",
        "optiona": "17",
        "optionb": "12",
        "optionc": "22",
        "optiond": "19",
        "correctAnswer": "d",
        "id": 11
      },
      {
        "title": "Mathe",
        "content": "19 + 3 =",
        "optiona": "22",
        "optionb": "11",
        "optionc": "24",
        "optiond": "23",
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "id": 12
      }
    ]
   
  }
  